Skills

Pyhton

C++

OOP

Django

DRF

GIT

Linux

PostgreSQL

HTML

Education

Wroclaw University of Science and Technology, Teleinformatyka 10/2020 – present | Wrocław, Poland

Informatic technologies, *Technical liceum* 02/2015 – 06/2020 | Lviv, Ukraine

Professional Experience

YT Group, *Trainee Python Backend Developer* 09/2021 – 05/2022 | Wrocław, Poland **Tasks/Achievements:**

- Creating apps and API endpoints for user working with system
- Developing API(using Django and Rest Framework for createCRUD)
- Design DB(PostgreSQL/SQL) majority with PGadmin4
- Investigated and fixed bugs in the Python backend
- · Working with git
- · Working with HTML

Freelance, *Python developer* 09/2020 – 09/2021

Developing web-applications on Django Developing telegram-bots

Petro Lemishko



+48730691492

Wróblewskiego 25

13/05/2002

https://github.com/petro-lemi

Languages

- Ukrainian
- Polish
- English

Profile

I have been programming for 3 years. That's how I learned how important it is teamwork. I know everyone has their jobs to do performance, which are as important as the tasks of the rest of the crew. I have good orientation in the field, I adapt quickly changing circumstances, I quickly establish a relationship and I remain composed in emergency situations.